jajah.com 2011-10-06

# JAJAH IP Telephony Platform / Low-Cost International Calls

The use of this website and its related software, upgrades or updates and all related services and special offers (the "Product") provided by JAJAH, Inc. are subject to the hereunder provisions of this Privacy Policy. 

JAJAH ("JAJAH" shall mean JAJAH Inc. and entities controlling, controlled by or under common control with JAJAH Inc.) is committed to safeguarding your privacy online for you, the user ("You" or "User"). 

Please read the following policy to understand how your personal information will be treated as You make full use of JAJAH’s Product as further detailed in the License Agreement. 

This policy may be updated from time to time and therefore, JAJAH asks You to check back periodically. Your continued use of the Product and JAJAH's site after this Privacy Policy has been amended shall be deemed to be your continued acceptance of the terms of this Privacy Policy, as amended. This Privacy Policy discloses the privacy practices for JAJAH’s web site and describes the information JAJAH collects about You and what may happen to such information. 

All capitalized terms and definitions in this Privacy Policy shall have the same meaning ascribed to them in the License Agreement, as applicable. 

As described below, some of your personal information is disclosed to third parties and used by JAJAH. By accepting the License Agreement, You consent to JAJAH’s use and disclosure of your personally identifiable information in accordance with the terms set forth herein. 

JAJAH participates in the Safe Harbor program developed by the U.S. Department of Commerce and the European Union. To view our certification, visit the U.S. Department of Commerce's Safe Harbor Web site http://www.export.gov/safeharbor. As part of its participation in the EU-U.S. Safe Harbor, JAJAH adheres to the Safe Harbor Privacy Principles of Notice, Choice, Onward Transfer, Security, Data Integrity, Access and Enforcement with respect to personal data transferred to the United States by JAJAH or its partners and service providers. 

**Information that JAJAH Collects**

Registration Data. JAJAH requires that You fill in the information marked as mandatory on the Registration Form at (the "Registration Data"). Such form may be updated by You from time to time. Automatic Tracking. By Using JAJAH’s site, JAJAH is able to and may track certain information about You and your correspondence on the JAJAH site in order to perform internal research on its Users' demographics, interests, and behavior, as well as to monitor and enforce the terms of the License Agreement. This information may include the URL from which You arrived, the next URL You may visit, what browser You are using and your IP address. Collecting Information. Information collected about You will be kept in a specific file for You. JAJAH may collect information about any activity being performed by You while using the Product, including any correspondence between you and other users of the JAJAH site, messages left by You on any board or any searches and requests performed by You. 

**Children's Information**

JAJAH's policy is that it does not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from subscribers under thirteen years of age. The Product is not directed or intended for children under thirteen years of age. If you are under thirteen years of age, you should not register to become a User or provide personally identifiable information on the side. If you are the parent or guardian of a User under the age of thirteen whom you believe has disclosed personally identifiable information to JAJAH, please contact JAJAH at support@jajah.com so that we may delete and remove such User's information from our system. 

**Cookies at JAJAH**

You acknowledge and agree that JAJAH may use cookies on its site. A cookie is a piece of text that can be entered into the memory of your hard drive and can store information about your use of JAJAH’s Product (the "Cookies"). The Cookies will help JAJAH make its services more convenient, personalized and more secure. In addition, Cookies may allow JAJAH to keep track and retrieve information about any User who acts in contradiction to JAJAH’s Privacy Policy and its License Agreement. If You would rather not have Cookies on your computer, You can usually set your browser to deny some but not all Cookies. You can also delete Cookies from your computer at your sole discretion. 

**JAJAH’s Usage of the Registration Data**

Internal Use. JAJAH uses the Registration Data about You for internal purposes, to improve its site and to better tailor the site to meet Your needs. In addition, JAJAH uses the Registration Data to analyze site usage and to deliver to You information about certain promotions, services or items that might interest You. In addition, JAJAH may use your e-mail address and, in rare situations your mailing address or phone number, to contact You regarding site notices from time to time. Editing Registration Data. You may review and edit your Registration Data by using your e-mail address or User ID and Password. If You cancel your account, You may also have your Registration Data deleted from JAJAH’s database by sending your request to support@jajah.com. However, You should be aware that once posted, You cannot change or remove any public postings made in JAJAH’s web site. You should also be aware that even if you delete your Registration Data, there may remain residual information that will remain within JAJAH's databases, access logs and other records, which may or may not contain personally identifiable information. Resolving Problems. JAJAH may use the Registration Data and other data it obtains from your current and past activities, to resolve disputes and troubleshoot problems and to monitor and enforce the License Agreement. In the event that You breach any of the terms of the License Agreement, JAJAH shall be entitled to use the Registration Data to locate You and pursue any necessary actions at its sole and absolute discretion in accordance with its Privacy Policy and the License Agreement. 

**JAJAH Disclosure of Users’ Registration Data General Rule.**

JAJAH will not disclose, sell or transfer any of your Registration Data, to any third parties (e.g., advertisers or business partners), except in the following cases: (i) JAJAH receives your permission; (ii) if JAJAH believes in good faith that the law requires such disclosure or transfer or (iii) as set forth below. JAJAH Community. You should be aware that in order to enjoy the Product, You will be required to disclose your e-mail address. As a result, other users of the JAJAH site as well as third parties might send You unsolicited e-mail. Third Parties. JAJAH may at any time add business partners or co-branded sites to its site, but the sharing of information with them will be limited to only statistical information regarding Users in general, and JAJAH will not disclose any of your Registration Data, correspondence or any related information. JAJAH assures You that in the event that JAJAH shall wish to transfer any of such information, JAJAH shall notify You before transferring such information, so that You will always have a chance to object to such transfer. Special Cases. JAJAH may also disclose Registration Data or other information, in special cases when it has reason to believe that disclosing such information is necessary to identify, contact or bring legal action against someone who may be violating JAJAH’s  License Agreement or this Privacy Policy or may be causing injury to or interference with (either intentionally or unintentionally), JAJAH’s rights or property, other users, or anyone else that could be harmed by such activities. In addition, JAJAH may disclose or access a User's account, in the event that JAJAH believes in good faith that the law requires such disclosure. You thus authorize JAJAH to disclose any information about You to law enforcement or other government officials if JAJAH, in its sole and absolute discretion, believes that such disclosure is necessary or appropriate. Although, JAJAH uses industry standard practices to protect your privacy, JAJAH does not ensure, and You should not expect, that your Registration Data or any private communications will always remain private. 

**Links and Displayed Sites.**

JAJAH’s site may contain links to other sites and may provide access to other sites displayed as search results. JAJAH is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such linked or otherwise displayed sites. Applicable Law. JAJAH's use of any information of a User is subject to the provisions of any applicable law. 

**User's Usage of Other Users' Registration Data**

Use of Users' Registration Data. JAJAH's Product may allow You limited access to other Users' Registration Data, personal information or other information ("Users' Information"). Such Users' Information, if disclosed to You, is disclosed to You only for the purpose of using the Product in accordance with the terms and conditions of the License Agreement and this Privacy Policy. 

You hereby agree that You shall use any Users' Information only: (a) in connection with the Product, and (b) for any other purpose that the owner of such information expressly agrees to. In all cases, you must comply with any request by any user to delete any Registration Data of such user from your database. In addition, under no circumstances, except as defined in this Section, may you disclose Registration Data of other users to any third party without JAJAH's express written consent and the express written consent of the relevant user. 

**Spam**

JAJAH and its Users do not tolerate spam. Therefore, without limiting the foregoing, You are not permitted to add any user, whose direct contact information was disclosed to you in connection with any use of the Product, to your mailing list without such user's express written consent after adequate disclosure. Password. Your JAJAH Registration Data is password-protected so that only You and JAJAH have access to this personal account. Since, You may edit your account by using your e-mail address or User ID and Password, JAJAH recommends that You not divulge your Password to anyone. 

**Disclosure of Information to Third Parties**

JAJAH's policy only addresses the use and disclosure of information JAJAH collects from You. To the extent that You disclose information to other parties on JAJAH’s site or to any other third party, different rules may apply to the use or disclosure of the personal information, which You disclose to them. Since JAJAH does not control the privacy policies of third parties, You are subject to the privacy customs and policies of such third parties. 

**Phone Calls**

Among the services JAJAH offers, Users may initiate phone calls between them which are partly or fully handled via JAJAH telecom partners. Therfore any information which You may post during such phone call, including any personal information shall not be deemed private. JAJAH cannot guarantee the security of such information, that you disclose or communicate in such phone call and you do so at your own risk. 

**Disclosure of Personal Information in the Event of a Merger or Sale of JAJAH**

JAJAH may merge or be acquired by another business entity or may sell all or substantially all of its assts to an acquirer. In the event of such merger, acquisition or sale, JAJAH may share some or all or your personally identifiable information with the acquiring company in order to continue serving you and others and continuing to offer you the Product. 

**Co-branded and Other Affiliated Sites**

As stated above, certain information or services offered or provided through this website, from time to time, may be provided on or through other websites operated by or in conjunction with third party providers ("Partners"). These websites and the features thereon may have the same "look and feel" as this website. JAJAH terms these websites "co-branded sites", and often times a Partner's logo or name may appear on the website, or the Partner's name may appear in the URL. Although JAJAH will continue to own any personally identifiable information collected about you from one of these co-branded sites, such information may be shared by JAJAH with that Partner. However, a Partner will not rent, sell, or disclose any of your personally identifiable information to third parties unless you consent to such disclosures and use in advance (for example, you may be asked to opt-in on a particular co-branded site in order to receive information or offers from a Partner, its affiliates or agents). 

**Security**

JAJAH’s site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the Registration Data. JAJAH uses industry standard efforts to safeguard the confidentiality of your Registration Data. Unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, while JAJAH strives to protect your personal information, JAJAH cannot ensure the security of any information that You transmit to JAJAH or any information that You receive from JAJAH’s Service, and You transmit such information at your own risk. Once JAJAH receives your transmission, it uses its commercial effort to ensure security on its systems. 

**Contact**

If You have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of JAJAH, or any related issues, JAJAH will be pleased to assist You. You may contact JAJAH at: 

JAJAH  
Privacy and Customer Care  
2513 E. Charleston Road, Suite 102  
Mountain View, CA 94043  
support@jajah.com.  
Phone: (650) 967-4357.

When we receive formal written complaints at this address, it is JAJAH’s policy to contact the complaining user regarding his or her concerns. We will cooperate with the appropriate regulatory authorities, including local data protection authorities, to resolve any complaints regarding the transfer of personal data that cannot be resolved between JAJAH and an individual. 

**Subordination to the License Agreement**

This Privacy Policy is incorporated into and subject to the terms and conditions of JAJAH’s License Agreement as an integral part thereof; in case of a contradiction between any provision of the License Agreement and the content of this document, the provisions of the License Agreement shall prevail. 

Effective Date: November 20, 2008
